oh is this the match you wanted to see
Subaru but Sarikawa tech manages to receive the ball
Nekama high school representing Tokyo and Sarikawa tech representing Ishikawa
both teams are known for demonstrating some of the toughest defense we'll see in this tournament
but only one will be powerful enough to earn them a place in the third round Joe
which squad is it going to be
Oh
Death from SQP
I'm a magic
I love you
A Moscou
ah our first nationals i just wish it could have been someplace we actually had to travel to
i'd like to ride on the bullet train one of these days well after this year
we won't get another chance where's this year's inner high tournament going to be held
we can ride it to cheer on our youngsters you're sure they'll get in have some faith
in the rising generation hey speaking of that's just the thing how could they even do that
he hates being in the spotlight but here we are dragging him to the national championship
yeah and i have to admit he definitely doesn't look like a championship athlete either i have like
no money it's the coast did you know the entire time he's been playing volleyball since middle school
kenma comes down with a fever anytime practice was especially hard or after a match and you know
since i'm the one who dragged him into it i always feel kind of guilty
but now we're here at nationals and that's a big deal so maybe he'll start thinking it's been worth
all the effort i mean that's what my hope is anyway yeah i don't know about that i don't think kenma
cares about that kind of stuff whatever you never know what could spark his interest
well just think about kenma's personality if he really hated playing he would have quit a long
time ago right dude kenma i told you no video games before bed you're going to end up getting a
horrible night's sleep yeah if i really want to quit playing then i will but it's also true that i would
probably feel kind of bad for abandoning kuro you would yeah i do actually care a little about other
people you know oh uh i know i'm just flattered to hear you say it i said probably and kinda
seriously just think about it for a second is it likely i practice for hours because i feel bad for
you obviously i wouldn't keep doing this if i didn't like it at the moment i still happen to be
playing volleyball i don't have a definitive reason to keep on playing but i don't really have a reason
to quit playing either i mean that's normal isn't it isn't it okay man touché typically rational
cut it out with the philosophy crap i really don't enjoy sweating or being out of breath at all
ever but i don't have any problems with leveling up
good night yeah good night
that kid may not have any stamina but he does have a weird kind of persistence
and he does manage to keep up with us at practice somehow even if he takes every chance to slack off
hang on this reminds me of the story you told me one time the crazy early riser thing
ah okay so kenma is a chronic oversleeper and he would regularly have his light on at five o'clock
in the morning i was sure he'd been up all night but he told me he actually woke up at 2 a.m to play
his video games he said his parents would throw his games out if he stayed up all night so he thought
he'd just wake up really early instead of course they found out and he got in trouble anyway point is
he'd never have done that for something he didn't like and then since we started practicing with
karasuno i think that he's been a lot more motivated yeah you're right maybe it's because
he's always hanging out with the little shrimp from there even though they're about as different as two
people can be well for one thing it's not often kenma makes new friends and i also think he might
see him as a valuable specimen a real-life boss that he wants to conquer strategically and as for the
shrimp well i bet he sees kenma as someone he wants to defeat at all costs kenma probably wouldn't
actually care if he did get knocked out so it wouldn't be very satisfying come on it's funny
though it really is such a kenma thing to call it leveling up
you want to go level up outside
yep
this isn't the time to be reminiscing about how much your underclassmen has grown
whatever yaku you ever heard of feelings before four days left in the spring nationals
and i'm gonna be the star i think we all know who the star is i'm even prepared for when the tv lady
wants an interview shut up astaxanthin man i said what are they arguing about oh just finish your damn
sorry you guys no it's fine what'd you say what's wrong with astaxanthin it's red our team color that's
it's not the issue here
sarukawa saw an opening but nekama shuts it down the nekama defenders will not let the ball fall to the court without a fight joe
and sarukawa is also keeping the ball in the air great job boys now just take your time i understand that sarukawa tech's coach shishio was at one time a student of nekama high school's coach nekama that's right joe perhaps that's where his emphasis on defense comes from
oh that's disgusting
huh what's the matter this whole game i feel like the sarukawa tech team has been deliberately avoiding going in for a quick point
oh yeah i couldn't tell i mean from what i've been able to see their attacks have actually been pretty vicious so far
well yeah of course they've been scoring i'm definitely not saying their offense has been weak or anything like that
plus nekama is being nekama they have high level defense and they can receive even the most flawless attacks
i don't know if that's the reason but to me it really looks like sarukawa isn't concerned about scoring so much as they're trying to disrupt nekama's rhythm
but what's the point if they don't score i imagine what they want is to keep the setter running
fukunaga
way to go
nice nice fukunaga nice nice fukunaga one more time
even if it means sacrificing the first set i want nekama's setter drained as much as possible
that kid he's probably not the type to let us break his spirit
but i bet he's the type to start slipping up when he gets tired
so we need to wear him down physically not mentally there's only one way to take out nekama
take out the brain
so
i hate running
but i do sort of like the scenery and the things i get to think about while i run
that ivy i can definitely climb that
and on top of that roof i bet i'll find a treasure chest
you
gut
baby yeah hey you're slow a whole lap behind catch back up to the group show some guts man
i don't like him
Yaku!
Nice receive!
A perfect A pass!
Heck yeah! Nekama's totally awesome!
I wanna sit down.
An A pass.
More like an A plus pass.
That's good.
Agh!
Huh?
Hagagai.
presence.
Kenma, don't think I'm gonna go all easy on you just because you're buddy-buddy with Kuro.
All right. What exactly does me being friends with Kuro have to do with anything?
Besides, this is just a passing drill.
He always looks so bored, and he talks so quiet, but he's actually pretty good, which is just not even fair.
You little piece of...
Wow. Would you look at those two? Go at it.
You could at least try to play well with the other kids sometimes.
Don't put this on me. That guy started it.
Yeah. I appreciate you refusing to back down from a fight, but still, I'm not asking you to be best friends with everybody, okay?
But these guys, they'll be around a lot, especially the ones in your year.
So, today was our first day as a newly formed team, and I know you're still adapting, but let's give it everything we've got, okay, boys?
Thank you, sir!
Hey, Yamamoto! You still out here doing a little running?
Yes, sir! See you later, sir!
Okay, Yamamoto. Don't overdo it.
Yes, sir!
Guts, baby!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Make sure you get all your stuff!
Yes, sir!
Hey, Kenma!
Great sets today.
Definitely. They were consistent and really easy to hit.
And your first practice match, too.
And pulling out that quick dump off when we were trailing was really badass!
Anyway, hope you keep up the great work out there.
This was my all-important practice match debut, but I couldn't stop hitting it out of bounds or into the net!
And worst of all...
I crashed into Kuro like an idiot!
We're heading out, guys!
Yamamoto, it was a mistake in a practice match. It happens, okay?
Yes, sir!
Good work, team!
Thanks!
Kuro! Coach wants to see you!
Coming!
You could at least try to play well with the other kids sometimes.
Uh, hey, Yamamoto.
Maybe you could try relaxing your shoulders when you're playing or whatever.
Oh, you mean the way you do.
Yeah, as if it's really that easy.
I'm trying to show everybody here how hard I've been working.
How exactly am I supposed to relax while I do that?
Uh...
Never mind.
The problem is that I just didn't have enough guts out there.
I think you should stop blaming something as vague as guts.
Try to identify a specific problem you can actually work on improving.
What?!
I focused too much on the ball.
I allowed the other team to provoke me.
I kept going for all the most difficult plays.
If you know all that stuff, then why do you blame everything on guts?
That means all that extra running and weight training you've been doing lately
wasn't about hard work, but your ego.
Okay, well, what about you?
You slacked off.
You could have gotten way more balls.
Yeah, but I was tired.
And even if I got them, they would have just been free balls for the other team.
Uh-oh.
Should we stop them?
This isn't a post-mortem anymore.
It's just a fight at this point.
Let them fight it out.
Sometimes you need that, honestly.
Don't try to talk to me about guts when you don't even have any!
I've had it up to here with your guts, Crap!
It means nothing!
It's not like they'll help you survive with one hit point or anything!
What the hell are you even talking about?!
If you're too obsessed with guts, you'll lose to a boss that you could have beaten!
What the hell do the bosses have to do with any of this?!
They're all in the stride!
All right, that's enough, you two!
When it is about guts!
Take it easy, Dostoyevsky!
Heh!
What?!
You what?!
Huh?!
Where do I even start?!
Toast-a-who?!
Who the hell's gonna clean this mess up?!
Sorry!
Holy crap, Fukunaga!
Someone's gonna have to get a mop!
And just what are you laughing at?!
You're pretty funny, Fukunaga.
What the hell is going on?!
I haven't yelled like that in ages.
I'm wiped.
Huh?
What the hell is going on?!
I haven't yelled like that in ages.
I'm wiped.
Huh?
Thank you!
I saw you n
What is with this guy this vibe it's not motivation or passion he just I don't know
He just really hates losing
Left side
Don't be lazy you were supposed to do an overhand there
He's on to me that one more step suddenly feels like a million miles. I wish I could stretch my arms like two meters
But the bastard still doesn't have any guts
Oh
Nice kill Yamamoto
That was really loud
The quality of our blocking it's starting to get to their number one
He's probably going to start trying to fake us out pretty soon and pay attention because they'll likely hit it out more
I'm glad he's not playing on the other team
Hey Kenma
You can call me Tora if you want. That's what all my friends call me
Uh, I don't have to do I
What the hell did you say? I'm trying to reach out of here
Tora
Coach Nekomata has always emphasized defense over all else in his setters. He looks for intelligence and game sense
It's a result of being so confident in his defender skills
We might not be able to crush the defense directly, but we can chip away at it bit by bit and if we can keep wearing them down
Then we'll see how weak their setter really is
Crush him
That setters been cobbled by those a passes for too long
Now crush him
When I want to touch wood
Yes
If you know what you see
You might be broken
That get to be
See you next time.
夢も叶うさ 心までやってきたのは 偶然なんかじゃなくて 去ってしまう舞台に立って 痛いといつでも強く願い続けた 君がそこにいたから
次回  TRAP